http://www.seroogys.com/customer-service/privacy-policy/

•
CUSTOMER SERVICE• Contact Us• Newsletter• Curbside & In-Store Pickup• Packaged Candy & Snacks• Locations & Hours• Ordering/Shipping• FAQ• Weather Alert
•
ABOUT US• Employment• News• Weekly Facebook Question Rules and Winners
1-800-776-0377
|
0
MY ACCOUNT•
FUNDRAISING
•
CUSTOMER SERVICE• Contact Us• Newsletter• Curbside & In-Store Pickup• Packaged Candy & Snacks• Locations & Hours• Ordering/Shipping• FAQ• Weather Alert
•
ABOUT US• Employment• News• Weekly Facebook Question Rules and Winners
1-800-776-0377
|
0
MY ACCOUNT
1-800-776-0377
|
0
MY ACCOUNT
1-800-776-0377
0
SIGNATURE GIFT BOXES- Assortments- Assorted- Classic- All Nut- Soft Centers- Truffles- Meltaways- Chocolate Meltaways- Mint Meltaways- Meltaway Sampler- Caramels & Fudge- Chocolate Covered Caramels- Chocolate Covered Fudge- Sea Salt Caramels- Nuts & Toffee- Nut Clusters- All Nut Assortment- Toffee- Snappers- Cashew- Pecan- Cashew Sea Turtles- Mixed- Fruit- Cherries- Apricots- Coconut- Sugar Free Chocolates- Assortment- Meltaways- Nut Clusters
SPECIALTY CHOCOLATES- Bars- Meltaways- Caramel- Pure Dark- Pure Milk- Sugar Free- Chocolate Shapes- Dark Chocolate- Milk Chocolate- White Chocolate- Individually Wrapped- Snappers- Caramel- Graham Crackers- Oreos- Peanut Butter- Pretzels- Toffee- Gift Boxes & Towers- Assortments- Angel Food- Caramel- Classy Brown Bag- Deluxe Caramel Corn- Fudge- Meltaways- Pretzels- Snappers- Truffles- Packaged- Caramel- Cookies- Pretzels- Fudge- Melting Chocolate- Hot Cocoa Mix
OCCASIONS- Holidays- Candy- Brittle- Chocolate- Chocolate Shapes- Gift Boxes- Holiday Meltaway Bars- Business Gifts- Assortments- Nuts- Towers & Baskets- Football- Candy- Chocolate- Gifts- Birthday- Gifts- Thank You- Gifts- Chocolate Cards- Weddings- Favors- Foiled Chocolates- Gifts
NUTS & SNACKS- Nuts- Gift Boxes- Gift Jars- Packaged- Snacks- Popcorn- Potato Chips- Snack Mixes- Candy- Salt Water Taffy
COFFEE- Flavored- Regular- Decaf- Unflavored- Regular- Decaf- Gifts- Candy- Baskets- Mugs
FUNDRAISING
CUSTOMER SERVICE- Contact Us- Newsletter- Curbside & In-Store Pickup- Packaged Candy & Snacks- Locations & Hours- Ordering/Shipping- FAQ- Weather Alert
ABOUT US- Employment- News- Weekly Facebook Question Rules and Winners
Customer Service » Privacy PolicyPrivacy Policy General
We at Seroogy's Chocolates are committed to respecting your privacy and recognizing your need for appropriate protection and management of personally identifiable information you share with us (the phrases "personally identifiable information" or "personal information" mean any information by which you can be identified, such as your name, address, telephone number, etc.). The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you of what personally identifiable information or personal information we may collect from you when you visit our web sites, how we use such information, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to review and correct, the information. This policy applies only to users accessing our web site from the United States.
As a part of our commitment to your privacy, Seroogy's Chocolates supports and adheres to the guidelines and practices adopted by the Direct Marketing Association's "Privacy Promise to American Consumers." We have agreed to (1) honor customers' requests not to share their information with other marketers; and (2) honor customers' requests not to receive mail, telephone or other solicitations from Seroogy's Chocolates. This agreement shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Wisconsin without giving effect to any principles of conflicts of law. If any provision of this Agreement shall be unlawful, void, or for any reason unenforceable then that provision shall be deemed severable from this Agreement and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions. This Site is operated by Seroogy's Chocolates from its offices within the state of Wisconsin, United States of America. Seroogy's Chocolates assumes no responsibility, and shall not be liable for any damages to, or viruses that may infect, your computer equipment or other property on account of your access to, use of, or browsing in the Site or your downloading of any Materials from the Site.
Collecting Information About You
In general, you can engage in many activities on this site without providing any personal information. We may track the Internet domain address from which people visit us and analyze this data for trends and statistics, but individual users will remain anonymous, unless you voluntarily tell us who you are. There may be times (such as when you purchase or order a product or subscribe to a newsletter, etc.) at which we ask you to provide certain information about yourself, such as your name, shipping/billing address, telephone number, email address, credit card information if making a purchase, birth date, and gender. We also maintain a record of your online product purchases. Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.
Using Information About You
We use the personally identifiable information you provide for internal purposes, such as confirming and tracking your order, analyzing trends and statistics, informing you of our new products, services and offers, and providing you with information from and about Seroogy's Chocolates. From time to time we might establish a business relationship with other persons or entities whom we believe trustworthy and whom we have asked to confirm that their privacy policies are consistent with ours. These are known as our Partners who may provide certain services including credit card processing, shipping, data management, promotional services, etc. We provide our Partners with the information needed for them to perform these services: Editing, Updating, Correcting and Deleting Information About You. We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive information from us contact us by email at seroogys@seroogys.com. Please include your email address, full name, and specifically what information you do not want to receive. If you would like to update or correct your email address, street address or other personal information with us please contact us the same way.
Please note that sometimes these requests may take up to 3-4 weeks to be effective, particularly if we are removing your name from mailings. In addition, when you purchase from us online or via telephone, mail or fax, or when you choose to enter a promotion, we may need to contact you via phone, email or mail to address questions or issues specific to your order, entry, etc., even if you have opted to not receive communications.
Please remember, if you delete certain information you may not be able to continue to purchase products or access other portions of our web site without entering additional information.
Cookies
Our web site may use "cookies." A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Generally, we use cookies to remind us of who you are, to tailor our products and services to suit your personal interests, estimate our audience size, assist our online merchants to track visits and to process your order, track your status in our promotions, contests and sweepstakes, and/or analyze your visiting patterns. You can generally set your browser to not accept cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it.
Security
We use sophisticated encryption and authentication tools to protect the security of your personal information that you share with us. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from our web sites, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we will do our best to protect its security on our systems.
We urge you to keep your password in a safe place and not to divulge it to anyone. Also remember to sign off your account and close your browser window when you have finished your visit. This is to ensure that others cannot access your account Restrictions on secondary use of our materials: The Site contains material which is derived in whole or in part from material supplied by Seroogy's Chocolates and other sources, and which may be protected by international copyright and trademark laws. No material (including but not limited to the text, images, audio and/or video) and no software (including but not limited to any images or files incorporated in or generated by the software or data accompanying such software) (individually and collectively the "Materials") may be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed in any way or decompiled, reverse engineered or disassembled, except that you may download one copy of the Materials on any single computer for your personal, non-commercial home use only, provided you keep intact all copyright and other proprietary notices. The use of any such materials on any other web site or networked computer environment is prohibited without the express written consent of Seroogy's Chocolates.
Outside Links
Our web sites may contain links to web sites operated and maintained by third parties, over which we have no control. Privacy policies on such linked sites may be different from our privacy policy. You access such linked sites at your own risk. We recommend that you check the privacy statement of other sites you visit before providing any personal information.
Policy Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy in whole or in part, we will inform you by posting a notice on our web site. Those changes will go into effect on the date posted in the notice. The new policy will apply to all current and past users of our web site and will replace any prior policies that are inconsistent. This policy was posted in September of 2005.
Copyright © 2020 Seroogy's
Privacy Policy
Designed & Powered By:
144 N. WISCONSIN ST.
DE PERE, WI 54115
STORE HOURS
784 WILLARD DR.
144 N. WISCONSIN ST.
DE PERE, WI 54115
STORE HOURS
784 WILLARD DR.
ASHWAUBENON, WI 54304
STORE HOURS
Copyright © 2020 Seroogy's
Privacy Policy
Designed & Powered By:
144 N. WISCONSIN ST.
DE PERE, WI 54115
STORE HOURS
784 WILLARD DR.
ASHWAUBENON, WI 54304
STORE HOURS
Copyright © 2020 Seroogy's
Privacy Policy
Designed & Powered By:
